Hari Sharma fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Personal records, 1949 - 2010; F-251-1; 1.25 m of textual records
  - Diaries and daily calendars, 1963 - 2008; F-251-1-3; 38 cm of textual records; Language: Some diary entries and notes in Hindi.
    - Diaries and daily calendars, vol. 1, 1963 - 1995; F-251-1-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 251-4)
      - Journal, 1991, F-251-1-3-0-2-18; Sharma, Hari (Artifact box - small 251-68)
        His research areas of special interest included political economy and agrarian social structures, particularly in India; social movements, political mobilization, ethnic and cultural identities; race and class; and nation-building among the aboriginal people of British Columbia. He wrote extensively on those topics and provided guest lectures at over 50 universities and scholarly institutions in Asia, Europe, and North America.
        In the spring of 1967, the Naxalbari peasant uprising inspired him to travel to India and several other Asian countries. Upon his return, he became committed to political activism from an anti-imperialist perspective. During 1971-72, Sharma was a founding member of and contributor to the Georgia Straight Collective, which produced a publication for radical and alternative views. In 1973, he went to Amnesty International in London and the Commission of Jurists in Geneva and made a written representation to the UN Human Rights Commission in an effort to publicize the condition of more than 30,000 political prisoners in Indian jails. In 1974, Sharma and his comrade Gautam Appa of the London School of Economics organized a petition of international scholars to protest the treatment of political prisoners in India, which he handed to the Indian Consulate in Vancouver, BC on August 15 of the same year.
        On a return trip from India in early 1975, Hari Sharma began to travel across North American campuses giving talks and mobilizing people toward the formation of a patriotic organization of Indians living in North America. This effort contributed to the founding of the Indian People's Association in North America (IPANA) on June 25, 1975, the same day on which Indira Gandhi declared a State of Emergency in India. The opposition to what was identified as a "fascist dictatorship" became the urgent task of IPANA along with the defense of the thousands of political prisoners.
        IPANA established chapters in several North American cities, with its most active chapters in Montréal, Vancouver, New York, Toronto, and Boston. It had links with patriotic organizations in San Francisco, Chicago, Winnipeg, and Edmonton. In their effort to oppose imperialism and to promote democratic rights and social justice in India, IPANA produced three publications: the quarterly New India Bulletin, which came out of Montréal from 1975; India Now, a monthly that was produced in New York from 1976; and Wangar, a Punjabi paper that was produced from Vancouver every two months from 1977. In addition to its publications, IPANA held numerous public meetings, demonstrations, lectures, films, and cultural programs to highlight the systemic oppression of dalits, peasants, and workers that mocked any concept of democracy and freedom put forth by the existing Government of India. One of IPANA’s first public interventions in North America was to sponsor a speaking tour by Mary Tyler, a British writer who had been held in an Indian prison for several years without any formal charge for alleged revolutionary activities in Bihar.
        Under Sharma's leadership, IPANA also supported the struggles of minorities and workers in BC. He was a primary force in the founding of the British Columbia Organization to Fight Racism (BCOFR). Through the 1980s, IPANA and BCOFR engaged thousands of people from several communities. Both Sharma and IPANA also helped form the Canadian Farmworkers Union in 1980.
        In the 1980s, Sharma focused much of his research and writing on the condition of minorities in India, which came to a crisis with the attack on the Golden Temple and the massacre of Sikhs in Delhi in 1984 following the assassination of Indira Gandhi. He defended the human rights of Sikhs and of Muslims who became the primary targets of the Hindutva movements advocating Hindu nationalism. In 1987, Sharma organized a parallel conference on the centralization of state power and the threat to minorities in India to coincide with the Commonwealth Conference in Vancouver.
        In 1989, Sharma united groups of the South Asian community to form the Komagata Maru Historical Society. The event commemorated the 75th anniversary of the Komagata Maru incident in which Indian immigrants traveling to Canada on a chartered ship were turned away from the shores of Vancouver by racist policies of the government. The society united the community, and as a result of its activities, the government installed a commemorative plaque in Vancouver in 1989. In 2004, during a screening of the film Continuous Journey (a documentary on the episode by the Toronto filmmaker Ali Kazimi), Mayor of Vancouver Larry Campbell sent a scroll to Sharma on behalf of the Komagata Historical Society declaring the week to be dedicated to the memory of Komagata Maru.
        Following the attack on the Babri Masjid mosque in December 1992, Hari Sharma became the prime mover in the formation of a North American organization dedicated to the defence of minority rights in India, also known as Non-Resident Indians for Secularism and Democracy (NRISAD). This organization united people of Indian origin collectively through educational and cultural activities. One of its significant events in Vancouver included the celebration of the 50th anniversary of India's independence from colonial rule. The event united people across the South Asian community to focus on issues that included the urgency for peace between Pakistan and India. In September 1999, Sharma travelled to Montréal to join the founding of the International South Asia Forum (INSAF), a coalition of individuals and organizations dedicated to the promotion of peace and social justice in South Asia. He became its first President and organized the Second Conference in Vancouver in August 2001.
        Over time, NRISAD recognized a need to widen the focus of the organization to include the whole of South Asia because its membership in Vancouver comprised people from the entire subcontinent of India and the diaspora in East Africa and other countries. Under Sharma's leadership, NRISAD evolved into the South Asian Network for Secularism and Democracy (SANSAD) in 2000. It pursued the same quest as its predecessors for peace and democracy based secularism, human rights, and social justice. Some activities included condemning the massacre of Muslims in Gujarat in 2002 (for which Sharma was denied a visa to visit India), championing the human rights of Kashmiris, condemning violence against journalists and academics in Bangladesh, supporting the movement for democracy and social justice in Nepal, and defending the human rights of Tamils under the attack of the Sri Lankan state.
        Throughout the years, Hari Sharma developed close ties and contacts with various political groups and communities. He worked with the First Nations in the Interior of BC, and as co-chair (along with Dr. Ronald Ignace, the elected Chief of the Skeetchestn Band from 1982 to 2003 and between 2007 and 2009), he helped to promote and to defend the merit of the SFU Kamloops First Nations program (then the SCES/SFU Program). In addition to his regular workload at SFU, Sharma taught courses such as Violence and War, Marxist Theory, and Third World issues on different occasions in Kamloops. Although the 16-year partnership between SFU and the Secwepemc Cultural Education Society of the Shuswap Nation (SCES) was dissolved by mutual agreement in 2004, over 400 students graduated from the program.
        In addition to his academic work and political activism, Hari Sharma was an accomplished literary writer and self-taught photographer. He wrote and published short stories in Hindi. Many of his works also were also translated into Bengali, Punjabi, and English. Vapsi, one of his stories, was made into a Doordarshan (Indian public service broadcaster) film. Sharma attributed his interest in photography to a Japanese camera that had been "gifted" to him as a bribe by an importer while pushing files as a government worker. The camera became something that Sharma frequently took with him on trips to India to capture snippets of everyday life. Over the years, his photographs were published in academic journals and art magazines. His works were also publicly displayed in galleries in North America, Europe, and India.
        After more than 50 years of political activity, Hari Sharma developed contacts and friendships with many who supported revolutionary movements. He married twice.
        After a prolonged battle with cancer, Hari Sharma died in his Burnaby home surrounded by his closest comrades on March 16, 2010.
    - Diaries and daily calendars, vol. 2, 1970 - 1989; F-251-1-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 251-5)
      - 1970, F-251-1-3-0-3-1
      - 1971, F-251-1-3-0-3-2
      - 1972, F-251-1-3-0-3-3
      - 1973, F-251-1-3-0-3-4
      - 1974, F-251-1-3-0-3-5
      - 1975, F-251-1-3-0-3-6
      - 1976, F-251-1-3-0-3-7
      - 1977, F-251-1-3-0-3-8
      - 1978, F-251-1-3-0-3-9
      - 1979, F-251-1-3-0-3-10
      - 1980, F-251-1-3-0-3-11
      - 1981, F-251-1-3-0-3-12
      - 1982, F-251-1-3-0-3-13
      - 1983, F-251-1-3-0-3-14
      - 1984, F-251-1-3-0-3-15
      - 1985, F-251-1-3-0-3-16
      - 1986, F-251-1-3-0-3-17
      - 1987, F-251-1-3-0-3-18
      - 1988 (was lost in May '88 but found again in '92), F-251-1-3-0-3-19
      - 1988-1989 weekly minder, F-251-1-3-0-3-20
      - 1989 weekly minder, F-251-1-3-0-3-21
    - Diaries and daily calendars, vol. 3, 1990 - 2008; F-251-1-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 251-6)
      - 1990 weekly minder, F-251-1-3-0-4-1
      - 1991-1992 Simon Fraser University, F-251-1-3-0-4-2
      - 1992 weekly, F-251-1-3-0-4-3
      - 1993 weekly, F-251-1-3-0-4-4
      - 1994 weekly appointments, F-251-1-3-0-4-5
      - 1995 weekly, F-251-1-3-0-4-6
      - 1996 weekly, F-251-1-3-0-4-7
      - 1996 (Yokohama notebook), F-251-1-3-0-4-8
      - 1997 weekly, F-251-1-3-0-4-9
      - 1998 weekly, F-251-1-3-0-4-10
      - 1999 weekly, F-251-1-3-0-4-11
  - Matrimonial records, 1990 - 2005; F-251-1-4; 25 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of personal records documenting Hari Sharma's marriages to Jyoti Sanghera and Sailani Jothi. Sub-series includes incoming and outgoing correspondence, notes, applications, certificates, and divorce records.
    Jyoti Sanghera; Sailani Jothi; Textual records
    - Personal correspondence regarding family, [ca 1990] - [ca 1996]; F-251-1-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 251-7)
    - Personal notes: "While I was gone to India", 1994; F-251-1-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 251-7)
    - Shalini - notes, 1994 - 2005; F-251-1-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 251-7)
    - Marriage certificate, 1995; F-251-1-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 251-7)
    - Shalini - immigration, 1995 - 1996; F-251-1-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 251-7)
    - Shalini - letters, 1995 - 2005; F-251-1-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 251-7)
    - Shalini - Citizenship application, 1999 - 2001; F-251-1-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 251-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: keep?.
    - My property and financial statement, 1993; F-251-1-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
    - Appeal, 1993; F-251-1-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
    - Reasons for "Order", 1993; F-251-1-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
    - Order, 1993; F-251-1-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
    - Statement of Facts, 1993; F-251-1-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
    - Affadavit - Karen Whiteley, 1993; F-251-1-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
    - Affadavit - Jyoti, 1993; F-251-1-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
    - Correspondence with Jyoti's lawyers, 1993; F-251-1-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
    - My answer and counter-petition, 1993; F-251-1-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
    - K. Whiteley Affadavit, Aug. 4, 1993; F-251-1-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
    - July 12 Affadavit - Jyoti, 1993; F-251-1-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
    - Petition of Divorce, 1993; F-251-1-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
    - Original maintenance demand, 1993; F-251-1-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
    - Jyoti - academia, 1990 - 1992; F-251-1-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
    - Tort, etc., 1994 - 1995; F-251-1-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
    - Jyoti - misc., 1993 - 1994; F-251-1-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 251-8)
  - Tax records, 1995 - 2006; F-251-1-5; 12 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of Hari Sharma's income tax records that he filed annually with the Canada Revenue Agency. Sub-series includes copies of assessments, audits, returns, and statements.
    Canada Revenue Agency; Textual records
    Some files may contain personal information, and access to these files may be restricted as stipulated by Archives policy. See the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
    - I. Tax 1995, F-251-1-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 251-9)
    - I. Tax 1996, F-251-1-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 251-9)
    - I. Tax 1997, F-251-1-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 251-9)
    - I. Tax 1998, F-251-1-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 251-9)
    - I. Tax 1999, 1999 - 2000; F-251-1-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 251-9)
    - I. Tax 2000, 2000 - 2001; F-251-1-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 251-9)
    - I. Tax 2001, F-251-1-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 251-9)
    - I. Tax Audit 2001-2, 2001 - 2002; F-251-1-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 251-9)
    - I. Tax 2002, 2002 - 2003; F-251-1-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 251-9)
    - I. Tax 2003, 2003 - 2004; F-251-1-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 251-9)
    - I. Tax 2004, 2004 - 2005; F-251-1-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 251-9)
    - I. Tax 2005, 2005 - 2006; F-251-1-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 251-9)
  - Education records, 1949 - 1964; F-251-1-6; 13 cm of textual records; Language: Some notes in Hindi.
    Sub-series consists of personal records made and/or received by Hari Sharma during his training at the Delhi School of Social Work and at Case Western Reserve University. Includes records he kept while conducting field work in India and the US. Sub-series includes notes, articles, publications, and notebooks.
    Delhi School of Social Work; Case Western Reserve University; Textual records
    Research associated with Sharma's Ph.D. dissertation is located in sub-series F-251-5-3, Socio-political writings.
    - Delhi School of Social Work application for admission and other supporting documentation, [ca 1949] - [ca 1960]; F-251-1-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 251-10)
    - Personal notebooks, [ca 1955] - [ca 1956]; F-251-1-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 251-10)
    - Notes found among education records, [ca 1958] - [ca 1960]; F-251-1-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 251-10)
    - Articles: Delhi villages, survey, assessment of social work training, memos, correspondence, [ca 1958] - [ca 1960]; F-251-1-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 251-10)
    - Notes: in Delhi, [ca 1960] - [ca 1961]; F-251-1-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 251-10)
    - Articles in print, [ca 1960] - [ca 1962]; F-251-1-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 251-10)
    - Notebook: Cleveland Hough Area, 1963; F-251-1-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 251-10)
    - Notebook: Goodrich-Bell Neighborhood Center, Cleveland, OH, 1963 - 1964; F-251-1-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 251-10)
    - Notebook: Schools' Committee Sequence, 1964; F-251-1-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 251-10)
    - Notebook: Street Club Presidents' League - Cleveland Hough Area, 1964; F-251-1-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 251-10)
- Correspondence, 1969 - 2009; F-251-2; 74 cm of textual records; Language: Some correspondence and notes in Hindi.
  Series consists of Hari Sharma's correspondence with friends, colleagues, and peers. Series includes incoming letters and copies of outgoing letters that reflect his teaching and research interests, his involvement in revolutionary movements, and his community activism. Also includes correspondence relating to research funding, publications, recommendations, and editorial work.
  The arrangement was provided by the archivist and based on the type of records in the series. Files are arranged chronologically.
  - Indian Organization North America, 1969 - 1983; F-251-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 251-11)
    Reviewed for access (Dec 12, 2023) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (1) that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (medical/psychological history). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
  - Bulletin of Concerned Asian Scholars (Editorial), 1974 - 1979; F-251-2-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 251-11)
  - Said/Shree/Montreal Unit, 1974 - 1983; F-251-2-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 251-11)
  - Movement Organizations, 1975 - 1980; F-251-2-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 251-11)
  - R. Bose/Montreal, 1975 - 1983; F-251-2-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 251-11)
  - Daya/Montreal, 1975 - 1984; F-251-2-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 251-11)
  - IPANA - General, 1975 - 1985; F-251-2-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 251-12)
  - Sudhir Joshi et al (Toronto), 1975 - 1985; F-251-2-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 251-12)
  - Bookstore Orders, etc., 1976 - 1980; F-251-2-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 251-12)
  - Victoria: Pritam S., 1976 - 1982; F-251-2-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 251-12)
  - Regina: Shreesh J., 1976 - 1987; F-251-2-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 251-12)
  - Calgary/Edmonton/Sas, 1976 - 1988; F-251-2-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 251-12)
  - Winnipeg: Darshan/Amarjit, 1976 - 1988; F-251-2-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 251-12)
  - Bulletin of Concerned Asian Scholars (Editorial), 1979 - 1988; F-251-2-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 251-12)
  - Van./BC, 1982 - 1988; F-251-2-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 251-12)
  - Paresh, 1983 - 1992; F-251-2-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 251-12)
  - Shalendra, 1984 - 1987; F-251-2-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 251-12)
  - Correspondence relating to publications, talks, journals, 1984 - 1996; F-251-2-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 251-13)
  - Pushpal Basu, 1985 - 1988; F-251-2-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 251-13)
  - Community contacts: Canada, 1987 - 1999; F-251-2-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 251-13)
  - Community contacts: U.S., 1987 - 1999; F-251-2-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 251-13)
  - Gobind Kelkar visit, 1988; F-251-2-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 251-13)
  - Saskatoon/Regina, 1988; F-251-2-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 251-13)
  - India: PCC work, 1988 - 1999; F-251-2-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 251-13)
  - Asia - general, 1988 - 1991; F-251-2-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 251-13)
  - India - other groups, 1988 - 1991; F-251-2-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 251-13)
  - Professional / Journals, 1989 - 1994; F-251-2-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 251-13)
  - India - friends, 1989 - 1998; F-251-2-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 251-13)
  - India - democratic people, 1989 - 1998; F-251-2-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 251-14)
  - Community contacts: Europe, 1989 - 1999; F-251-2-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 251-14)
  - India - PCC, 1989 - 2001; F-251-2-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 251-14)
  - Indian Government: Visa problem, 1990; F-251-2-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 251-14)
  - India - Film makers, 1990; F-251-2-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 251-14)
  - Friends/Contacts: Local BC, 1990 - 1997; F-251-2-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 251-14)
  - India - editors, etc., 1990 - 1999; F-251-2-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 251-14)
  - Correspondence found in box of Communist literature, 1991; F-251-2-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 251-14)
  - 1991 Connector Letters, F-251-2-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 251-14)
  - Correspondence to Hari Sharma regarding Native Management and Economic Development Program, 1991; F-251-2-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 251-14)
  - Shuswap contacts and information, 1991 - 1995; F-251-2-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 251-14)
  - India - movement people/groups, 1991 - 1996; F-251-2-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 251-15)
  - Rajendra Yadav, 1991 - 1998; F-251-2-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 251-15)
  - ICBC (deer) - personal/business, 1991 - 1999; F-251-2-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 251-15)
  - Smitu Kothari, 1992 - 1993; F-251-2-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 251-15)
  - Ramadhar Foundation, 1992 - 1993; F-251-2-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 251-15)
  - Email from Balaji regarding Indian politics, 1993; F-251-2-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 251-15)
  - Gobinda Mukhoty correspondence, 1993 - 1995; F-251-2-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 251-15)
  - Sonal - Shastri, 1993 - 1995; F-251-2-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 251-15)
  - Activism/political work, 1993 - 1999; F-251-2-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 251-15)
  - Book reviews for International Journal of Punjab Studies, 1994; F-251-2-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 251-15)
  - India - academic, 1994 - 1995; F-251-2-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 251-15)
  - Manju - masks, 1994 - 1996; F-251-2-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 251-15)
  - BCAS debate - May/June 1995, F-251-2-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 251-15)
  - Emails fowarded by colleagues re. conferences, campaign, call to action, 1996; F-251-2-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 251-16)
  - Vancouver scene, 1996 - 2005; F-251-2-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 251-16)
  - India, 1996 - 2007; F-251-2-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 251-16)
  - North America, 1996 - 2008; F-251-2-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 251-16)
  - Asia/Europe, 1997 - 2004; F-251-2-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 251-16)
  - Granting of Professor Emeritus status by SFU, 1998 - 1999; F-251-2-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 251-16)
  - Re. photographos on display in Bennett Library foyer, 1999; F-251-2-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 251-16)
  - India, 2003 - 2009; F-251-2-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 251-16)
  - Re. nomination of Dr. Marianne Boelscher Ignace for CUFA-BC Academic of the Year Award, 2004; F-251-2-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 251-16)
  - Recommendation for admission to SFU's graduate program in Sociology, 2004; F-251-2-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 251-16)
  - SFU research funding application to India for conferences, 2007; F-251-2-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 251-16)
  - Mary Tyler, 1973 - 1985; F-251-2-0-0-64; Martin, A. (Artifact box - small 251-69)
    Photographic materials; Textual records
  - K. Raj, EPW, 1974 - 1987; 251-2-0-0-65 (Artifact box - large 251-70)
  - Samar Sen / Frontier, 1974 - 1987; 251-2-0-0-66 (Artifact box - large 251-70)
  - India Inner, 1975 - 1979; F-251-2-0-0-67 (Artifact box - large 251-70)
  - Editors, 1975 - 1985; F-251-2-0-0-68 (Artifact box - large 251-70)
  - Arund (Patuna), 1986 - 1987; F-251-2-0-0-69 (Artifact box - large 251-70)
  - Mukundan Menon, 1975 - 1987; F-251-2-0-0-70 (Artifact box - large 251-70)
  - Political Activists (India), 1975 - 1988; F-251-2-0-0-71 (Artifact box - large 251-70)
  - Arun Shouri, People's Union for Civil Liberties, 1981 - 1982; F-251-2-0-0-72 (Artifact box - large 251-70)
  - Ashok Jhunjhunwala, 1976 - 1987; F-251-2-0-0-73 (Artifact box - large 251-70)
  - Suresh, 1975 - 1988; F-251-2-0-0-74 (Artifact box - large 251-70)